<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>HowToPhil</title>
  <link>http://howtophil.com/</link>
  <description>Has the skill</description>
  <generator>BlazeBlogger 1.2.0</generator>
  <item>
    <title>Wakeshma Township Board is targeting my family: Petition</title>
    <link>http://howtophil.com/2018/02/9-wakeshma-township-board-is-targeting-my-family-petition/</link>
    <guid>http://howtophil.com/2018/02/9-wakeshma-township-board-is-targeting-my-family-petition/</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>
The Wakeshma Township Board believes they have the right and authority to have everything we own torn down and then to assess liens against our property. This will take from my family everything we own and leave us with nothing.
</p>
<p>
Small town governments become more corrupt every day. If you believe that this obvious and outright theft from citizens is wrong, then please sign this petition. Let the Wakeshma Township Board and their hired officials know that you stand with the Rhoades family, that you stand against persecution of poor families and the theft of their land.
</p>
<p>
If we don't stand together, we all fall.
</p>
<p>
You don't have to live in Wakeshma Township or even in Michigan to sign the petition. This kind of thing is happening all over the country. We need to start standing up to these corrupt small town "governments" together or they will continue to attack all of us.
</p>
<p>
Thank you for any support you can lend.
</p>

    ]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Book: Burgundy Wolf: The Case of the One Eyed Woman</title>
    <link>http://howtophil.com/2016/05/8-book-burgundy-wolf-the-case-of-the-one-eyed-woman/</link>
    <guid>http://howtophil.com/2016/05/8-book-burgundy-wolf-the-case-of-the-one-eyed-woman/</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>
<a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01FRG9NSQ"><img src="/images/bwcoew.jpg"></a>
</p>
<p>
Burgundy Wolf, a private detective working the streets, slums, and sky-rises of Heartbeat City, sits in his office with his trusty dog, waiting for the next case to arrive.
</p>
<p>
A knock on the door. The corpse of a woman with a bullet through one eye. A phone call telling him that they have stolen his gun, used it to murder her, and stashed it where the cops will find it.
</p>
<p>
The Wolf must take to the streets to clear his name and perhaps even put a stop to a plot that endangers the entire city.
</p>
<p>
<a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01FRG9NSQ">You can get this book on Amazon Kindle or in print</a>.
</p>
    ]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Book: Never Alone The First Lightning Bug</title>
    <link>http://howtophil.com/2016/05/7-book-never-alone-the-first-lightning-bug/</link>
    <guid>http://howtophil.com/2016/05/7-book-never-alone-the-first-lightning-bug/</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://www.amazon.com/Never-Alone-First-Lightning-Bug-ebook/dp/B00AH9VV48"><img src="/images/neveralone.jpg"></a></p>
<p>
I'd like to share a story about these stories with you. :)
</p>
<p>
My sister and her daughter, my niece, were visiting the other day. My niece is about one year old, with cute chubby cheeks, and a quirky attitude.
</p>
<p>
I was working on my Japanese language study when she wandered into my room carrying “Never Alone & The First Lightning Bug” (the children’s book I had recently published and had given copies of to my nieces and nephews for Christmas). She looked up at me, waved the blue and orange book around and said, “Book! Book!” which is her way of asking me to read to her. So of course I stopped my studies, pulled her up on to my lap, and read my stories to her. My sister says that she does this at home all the time too, which makes me super happy. I take it as a sign that I’ve crafted something children love.
</p>
<p>
I’ve set the price of “Never Alone & The First Lightning Bug” to just $0.99 for the Amazon Kindle version, because I believe that once you have read it to your children they’ll ask for it again and again, after all my nieces and nephews sure do. The printed and bound “real book” version is more, because printing and binding is an expensive process, but you just might decide you want that printed version so your child can read these stories to your grandchildren some day.
</p>
<p>
The minimalistic illustrations, while great for children, are sometimes met with less than the greatest enthusiasm by adults. That’s okay, I wrote and illustrated these stories for children. I’m the second oldest of seven children, my first jobs were babysitting my cousins and the kids down the street- I know what children like to read. I’ve been reading stories to and making up stories to tell children for most of my life. Kids in the one to five age range love minimalistic and uncluttered illustrations, these are the types of books they would pick out and bring to me again and again.
</p>
<p>
In this book you will find two wonderful stories. The first is the story of a little boy named Alone, a little girl named Never and how they have a positive effect on each other. The other explores the origin of the lightning bug in a fanciful way (loosely based on ancient myths of the beginning of the world) that will appeal to children of all ages.
</p>
<p>
<a href="https://www.amazon.com/Never-Alone-First-Lightning-Bug-ebook/dp/B00AH9VV48">You can get this book on Amazon for Kindle or in print</a>.
</p>

    ]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Bitvote Poll: Taylor Swift or Nicky Minaj, who is crazier?</title>
    <link>http://howtophil.com/2015/07/6-bitvote-poll-taylor-swift-or-nicky-minaj-who-is-crazier/</link>
    <guid>http://howtophil.com/2015/07/6-bitvote-poll-taylor-swift-or-nicky-minaj-who-is-crazier/</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Cast your vote with some Bitcoin.</p>

<div id="bitvote">
        <script>
		var question = "Who is crazier, Nicki Minaj or Taylor Swift?";
		var addpos = "13UUaxcfGVUAbNcK93PGnbwf3TLaYSymMS";
		var addneg = "1Ci9SsaX5TUsmNhY34G49k1phqa8kCnKH2";
		var addsnark = "1CxSMffZ4x7rP1SrpPqTZ4EMhHWX7QG2CE";
		document.write("<hr><h3>Question: " + question + "</h3>");

		var xmlHttp = new XMLHttpRequest();
		xmlHttp.open( "GET", "https://blockchain.info/q/getreceivedbyaddress/" + addpos, false );
		xmlHttp.send( null );
		document.write("Vote for Taylor Swift by sending Bitcoin to:<br><font size=2>" + addpos + "</font><br>");
		document.write("<img src='https://blockchain.info/qr?data=" + addpos + "&size=100'><br>");
		document.write("Satoshi Votes: ");
		document.write(Number(xmlHttp.responseText).toLocaleString());
		document.write("<br><br>");

		var xmlHttp = new XMLHttpRequest();
		xmlHttp.open( "GET", "https://blockchain.info/q/getreceivedbyaddress/" + addneg, false );
		xmlHttp.send( null );
		document.write("Vote Nicki Minaj by sending Bitcoin to:<br><font size=2>" + addneg + "</font><br>");
		document.write("<img src='https://blockchain.info/qr?data=" + addneg + "&size=100'><br>");
		document.write("Satoshi Votes: ");
		document.write(Number(xmlHttp.responseText).toLocaleString());
		document.write("<br><br>");

		var xmlHttp = new XMLHttpRequest();
		xmlHttp.open( "GET", "https://blockchain.info/q/getreceivedbyaddress/" + addsnark, false );
		xmlHttp.send( null );
		document.write("I'll Bitvote you!:<br><font size=2>" + addsnark + "</font><br>");
		document.write("<img src='https://blockchain.info/qr?data=" + addsnark + "&size=100'><br>");
		document.write("Satoshi Votes: ");
		document.write(Number(xmlHttp.responseText).toLocaleString());
		document.write("<br><br>");
        </script>
</div>
    ]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>How To Turn A Furoshiki Or Square Cloth Into A Two Handle Purse</title>
    <link>http://howtophil.com/2010/10/5-how-to-turn-a-furoshiki-or-square-cloth-into-a-two-handle-purse/</link>
    <guid>http://howtophil.com/2010/10/5-how-to-turn-a-furoshiki-or-square-cloth-into-a-two-handle-purse/</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2010 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>
<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KmffZzU6Q0M" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</p>
    ]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>How To Use Furoshiki Or Square Cloth As A Reusable Grocery Bag</title>
    <link>http://howtophil.com/2010/10/4-how-to-use-furoshiki-or-square-cloth-as-a-reusable-grocery-bag/</link>
    <guid>http://howtophil.com/2010/10/4-how-to-use-furoshiki-or-square-cloth-as-a-reusable-grocery-bag/</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2010 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>
<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/VPQJa2plMFE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</p>
    ]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>How To Use A Furoshiki Or Square Cloth To Carry Two Books</title>
    <link>http://howtophil.com/2010/10/3-how-to-use-a-furoshiki-or-square-cloth-to-carry-two-books/</link>
    <guid>http://howtophil.com/2010/10/3-how-to-use-a-furoshiki-or-square-cloth-to-carry-two-books/</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2010 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>
<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KD1-G6iybds" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</p>
    ]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>How To Use A Furoshiki Or Square Cloth To Carry Two Bottles</title>
    <link>http://howtophil.com/2010/10/2-how-to-use-a-furoshiki-or-square-cloth-to-carry-two-bottles/</link>
    <guid>http://howtophil.com/2010/10/2-how-to-use-a-furoshiki-or-square-cloth-to-carry-two-bottles/</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2010 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>
<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/XbFjCybyKIU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</p>
    ]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>How To Turn A Furoshiki Or Square Cloth Into A Single Handled Purse</title>
    <link>http://howtophil.com/2010/10/1-how-to-turn-a-furoshiki-or-square-cloth-into-a-single-handled-purse/</link>
    <guid>http://howtophil.com/2010/10/1-how-to-turn-a-furoshiki-or-square-cloth-into-a-single-handled-purse/</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2010 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>
<iframe width="560" height="315" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/ytyAxsmdoGc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</p>
<br>
    ]]></description>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>